<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>All Posts - Thomas Bates III</title>
        <link>https://thomasbates.info/posts/</link>
        <description>All Posts | Thomas Bates III</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><managingEditor>tebates@proton.me (Thomas Bates)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>tebates@proton.me (Thomas Bates)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 20:26:35 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thomasbates.info/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Three Parades</title>
    <link>https://thomasbates.info/posts/three-parades/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 20:26:35 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Thomas Bates</author>
    <guid>https://thomasbates.info/posts/three-parades/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>I started to write something highfalutin about the progression of Pride, Protest, and the Military parade that happened in DC last week. I had nearly 3000 words written, but it felt disjointed, overstuffed, and unfocused. Unfixable.</p>
<hr>
<!-- raw HTML omitted -->
<p><a href="https://www.flickr.com/photos/tbindc/albums/72177720326980652" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">View the Album on Flickr</a></p>
<p>I do not know how to reconcile that a Pride parade happened in Washington D.C. at the same time as Federal programs are eradicating sexual orientation and gender identity data from their datasets. I am not sure what I should take away from a Starbucks float rolling down 14th street while a few blocks away someone is cooking up a plan to strip resources for queer people out of the 988 hotline.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Two Critiques of the Proposed Social Work Licensure Compact</title>
    <link>https://thomasbates.info/posts/two_critiques/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 20:18:18 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Thomas Bates</author>
    <guid>https://thomasbates.info/posts/two_critiques/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>The Council of State Governments (CSG), Department of Defense (DoD), and the Association of Social Work Boards (ASWB) have partnered to draft an interstate licensure compact for social workers. The Compact is currently available in draft for <a href="https://compacts.csg.org/compact-updates/social-work/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer ">public comment</a>.</p>
<p>Many professions have interstate compacts allowing work and life to flow across State lines. Some large organizations (such as the VA) already accept out-of-State licenses. The proposal, as written, would undoubtedly make the practice of social work significantly easier for many social workers. However, the proposal does not meaningfully support new social workers or macro workers. It also fails to protect all social workers from the piling on of many (many) fees across States, but letting States squeeze underpaid social workers for cash is perhaps a requirement if we want something like the Compact.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Ban Source of Income Discrimination in Illinois</title>
    <link>https://thomasbates.info/posts/source_of_income_article/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 16:02:00 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Thomas Bates</author>
    <guid>https://thomasbates.info/posts/source_of_income_article/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Source of Income Discrimination is one of the most significant barriers to housing people experiencing homelessness, right behind lack of affordable housing. The concept behind a housing voucher is, essentially, to make housing that is unaffordable become affordable. There is already a significant shortage of affordable housing<sup id="fnref:1"><a href="#fn:1" class="footnote-ref" role="doc-noteref">1</a></sup> throughout Illinois, and not enough serious policy effort aiming to affect this shortage.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, since the pandemic’s beginning, we have seen a huge influx of financial resources to organizations working to end homelessness. These new programs are often authorized with very little consideration for how they will interact and compete with one another, let alone the needs of the clients they are expected to serve. Yet, the dollar amounts attached to them are tremendous. Here’s a short list<sup id="fnref:2"><a href="#fn:2" class="footnote-ref" role="doc-noteref">2</a></sup>:</p>]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
